<resources>
    <string name="app_name">JUET</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="about_us">Jaypee University of Engineering &amp; Technology, Guna has been established vide Government of Madhya Pradesh gazette extra ordinary No.3 of 2010 dated 29th April 2010 as a private university in the State of MP under the provisions of MP Niji Vishwavidyalaya Adhiniyam 2007. The university has been notified by the UGC under section 2(f) of the UGC Act, 1956 and Accredited by NAAC with Grade “A” in very first cycle of Accreditation in 2016. This University is sponsored by Jaypee Group.. It was earlier Jaypee Institute of Engineering and Technology, Guna, established in the year 2003 based on the MOU signed between Jaiprakash Sewa Sansthan (a not-for-profit trust) and the Government of Madhya Pradesh with an aim of becoming a Center of Excellence in Engineering and Technology in MP.
                            This is one of the four Universities established for imparting Engineering education by the Jaiprakash Sewa Sansthan (JSS), an educational initiative which recognizes the role of IT and emerging technologies in improving the quality of life of the people of India. JUET\'s location at Raghogarh, in Guna district, is a well thought out as it serves backward district of MP such as Shivpuri, Gwalior, Sheopur, Ashoknagar, Sagar, Rajgarh, Vidisha etc. This region, currently in a rural setting with strong agricultural activities is likely to grow as a major industrial hub. JUET is being developed as a major center to provide competent, well trained technical manpower to the region.
                            \nDevelopers Nikhil sharma,Aditya dhimole\n\n


    </string>
    <string name="title_about_us">About us</string>
    <string name="webView">WebView</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="search_below"> Search Below</string>


</resources>
